
//This is a geography/political quiz about the 10 nations of the world with the highest GDP (Gross Domestic Product)
        //some questions will be multiple choice, and some only true/false. Good Luck!

{
"response_code":0,
"results":[
{
"type":"boolean", //USE THIS AS A MODEL, THERE ARE TRUE AND FALSE QUESTIONS AND MULTIPLE CHOICE
"question":"The captial of the United States of America is New York City, New York",
"correct_answer":"False",
"incorrect_answers":[
"True",
]
},
{
"type":"boolean",
"question":"In China, you find the manufacturing city of Shenzhen(深圳)",
"correct_answer":"True",
"incorrect_answers":[
"False",
]
},
{
"type":"boolean",
"question":"Japan's largest metropolitan area is Osaka",
"correct_answer":"False",
"incorrect_answers":[
"True"
]
},
{
"type":"boolean",
"question":"Germany has the largest GDP (Gross Domestic Product) out of any nation in the European Union",
"correct_answer":"True",
"incorrect_answers":[
"False"
]
},
{
"type":"multiple",
"question":"The historical landmark Stonehenge can be found in Great Britain, United Kingdom",
"correct_answer":"True",
"incorrect_answers":[
"False",
]
},
{
"type":"multiple",
"question":"What is India's most-followed religion?",
"correct_answer":"Hinduism",
"incorrect_answers":[
"Islam",
"Christianiy",
"Jainism"
]
},
{
"type":"multiple",
"question":"5 of France's Integral Regions (similar to counties within a state) are not in contiguous France... Which of these islands belongs to France?",
"correct_answer":"Guadeloupe",
"incorrect_answers":[
"Ibiza",
"Mallorca",
"Corsica"
]
},
{
"type":"multiple",
"question":"What is the capital of Brazil",
"correct_answer":"Brasilia",
"incorrect_answers":[
"Rio de Janeiro",
"São Paulo",
"Belo Horizonte"
]
},
{
"type":"multiple",
"question":"Italy shares a land border with 6 countries. All of these are in the continent of Europe, but how many of these are in the European Union?",
"correct_answer":"3",
"incorrect_answers":[
"2":
"4",
"5",
]
},
{
"type":"multiple",
"question":"Canada may be the second largest country in the world by area, but Russia is about how many square miles larger than Canada?",
"correct_answer":"2.7 million",
"incorrect_answers":[
"270 thousand",
"27 million",
"27 Thousand"
]
}
}